Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. 16mm Microfilm As-Broadcast Scripts, 1928-1958 RL.00655
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
J. Walter Thompson Company. 16mm Microfilm As-Broadcast Scripts
1928-1958
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
J. Walter Thompson Company
RL.00655
3 Linear Feet 292 items
Founded in 1864, the J. Walter Thompson Company (JWT) is one of the oldest and largest enduring advertising agencies in the United States. The J. Walter Thompson Company (JWT) 16mm Microfilm As-Broadcast Scripts span the years 1928-1958 and contain transcripts of radio and television dramas and variety shows, news programs, commercials, and sports programming. Companies featured include Andrew Jergens, Ballantine, Brillo, Ciba-Geigy, Fannie Farmer, Ford, General Cigar, J.B. Williams, Kodak, Kraft, Lamont-Corliss (Pond's), the New York Yankees, Penick & Ford (Br'er Rabbit), Standard Brands, the U.S. Marine Corps, and Wrigley. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Provenance
The J. Walter Thompson Company. 16mm Microfilm As-Broadcast Scripts were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 1987.
Collection Overview
The J. Walter Thompson Company (JWT) 16mm Microfilm As-Broadcast Scripts span the years 1928-1958 and contain transcripts of radio and television dramas and variety shows, news programs, commercials, and sports programming. Companies featured include Andrew Jergens, Ballantine, Brillo, Ciba-Geigy, Fannie Farmer, Ford, General Cigar, J.B. Williams, Kodak, Kraft, Lamont-Corliss (Pond's), the New York Yankees, Penick & Ford (Br'er Rabbit), Standard Brands, the U.S. Marine Corps, and Wrigley.
Collection Arrangement
Arranged by reel number, and physical sequence of the scripts therein. Original documents were microfilmed in no order, so scripts relating to a particular client or program are scattered throughout the collection. The collection described here represents a portion of the whole 16mm microfilm collection.
Related Material
Related materials may be found in other collections of the J. Walter Thompson Company Archives:
Carroll Carroll Papers
Dan Seymour Papers
Jack Hilton Papers
John F. Devine Papers
Lois Gaeta Papers
Maury Holland Papers
Television advertising; Television advertising -- United States -- History; Television advertising -- United States; Radio broadcasting of sports -- United States; Radio broadcasting -- United States -- History -- 20th century; Radio programs; Radio plays; Radio broadcasting -- 1950-1960; Radio broadcasting -- 1940-1950; Radio broadcasting -- United States -- History; Radio broadcasting -- United States; Advertising agencies; Advertising -- United States -- History; Advertising -- United States; Advertising; Radio advertising -- United States; Radio advertising; Advertising agencies -- United States -- History; Advertising agencies -- United States; Radio broadcasting -- 1930-1940; Radio broadcasting -- 1920-1930; Radio broadcasting; Radio advertising -- United States -- History; Television broadcasting -- United States -- History -- 20th century..; Television broadcasting -- United States -- History; Television broadcasting -- United States; Television broadcasting; Television programs; Television broadcasting of sports -- United States; Microfilms; Television scripts; Radio scripts; Ford Motor Company; General Cigar Company (Philadelphia, Pa.); J. Walter Thompson Company; J.B. Williams Co; John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History; Kraft Foods Company; New York Yankees (Baseball team); Andrew Jergens Company (Cincinnati, Ohio); Chesebrough-Pond's.; CIBA-GEIGY Corporation; Eastman Kodak Company; Penick & Ford, Ltd; P. Ballantine & Sons; United States. Marine Corps; Standard Brands Incorporated; Wm. Wrigley Jr. Company
- Advance program announcement, 1941-1942; 1
  - Ballantine Three Ring Time, 1941 Aug.; Nov. (Film-reel 171)
  - Chase & Sanborn Coffee, 1941 Aug.; Dec. (Film-reel 171)
  - Chase & Sanborn Coffee, 1942 Aug. 31 (Film-reel 171)
  - Chase & Sanborn--One Man's Family, 1942 Aug. 31 (Film-reel 171)
  - Columbia Network, 1941 Aug. 212 (Film-reel 171)
  - Johns-Manville--De Mille, 1941 Aug. 22 (Film-reel 171)
  - Johns-Manville--Frazier Hunt, 1941 Oct. 10 (Film-reel 171)
  - Lorillard--Old Gold cigarettes, 1941 Jan.-Apr. (Film-reel 171)
  - Lux Radio Theatre, 1941 Aug. 27 (Film-reel 171)
  - Old Gold cigarettes (Lorillard), 1942 Jan.-Apr. (Film-reel 171)
  - True or False, 1941 June-Dec. (Film-reel 171)
  - Ward's Tip Top Bread--Terry and the Pirates, 1942 Apr. 21 (Film-reel 171)
  - White Owl cigars, 1941 Aug. 26 (Film-reel 171)
  - White Owl cigars, 1942 Dec. 8 (Film-reel 171)
- Alphabetical Scripts, 1953; 2
  - Allsweet to Ballantine, 1953 (Film-reel 984)
  - Ballantine to Johns-Manville, 1953 (Film-reel 985)
  - Johns-Manville to Kraft, 1953 (Film-reel 986)
  - Kraft to end, 1953 (Film-reel 987)
- Andrew Jergens, 1931-1936; 3
  - Programming, 1931-1932; 1
    - La Gerardine Program, 1931 Mar. -June1933 Feb.-Apr. (Film-reel 10)
    - Ray Perkins, 1932 Jan.-May (Film-reel 244)
  - The Jergens Program, 1931-1936; 2
    - Cornelia Otis Skinner, 1935 June-Aug. (Film-reel 10)
    - Ray Perkins, 1931 June-Dec. (Film-reel 9)
    - Walter Winchell, 1932 Dec.1933 Sept.-1936 Feb. (Film-reel 9)
    - Walter Winchell, 1935-1936 (Film-reel 10)
- Auditions, 1934-1944; 4
  - Crossroads USA, 1940; 3
    - American Dairy Association, 1940 July 17 (Film-reel 171)
    - Bab-O, 1940 Aug. 9 (Film-reel 171)
    - Bromo-Seltzer (Emerson Drug), 1940 July 19 (Film-reel 171)
    - Gillette blades, 1940 Aug. 8 (Film-reel 171)
    - Kellogg's Corn Flakes, 1940 July 19 (Film-reel 171)
    - Old Gold cigarettes (Lorillard), 1940 July 19 (Film-reel 171)
    - Schick razor, 1940 July 19 (Film-reel 171)
    - Script (no commercials or clients), 1940 Dec. 7 (Film-reel 171)
    - Sealtest Ice Cream (Sheffield), 1940 Aug. 8 (Film-reel 171)
    - Wrigley Doublemint gum, 1940 July 23 (Film-reel 171)
  - Eastman Kodak, 1942; 4
    - Aetna Life Affiliated Companies, 1942 Aug.-Sept. (Film-reel 171)
    - Lifebuoy, 1942 Aug. 28 (Film-reel 171)
    - Musical Pictures, 1942 Sept. 13 (Film-reel 171)
    - Pennsylvania Anthracite, 1942 Jan. 6 (Film-reel 171)
  - Lever Brothers, 1939-1942; 5
    - All This and Heaven Too, 1939 (Film-reel 171)
    - Family Man, 1939 Jan. 9 (Film-reel 171)
    - John Doe American, 1942 Mar. (Film-reel 171)
    - Life and Loves of Dr. Susan, 1939 Jan.-Feb. (Film-reel 171)
    - Lux Radio Fiction Club, 1939 (Film-reel 171)
    - Wayne King and Frank Luther, approximately 1940 (Film-reel 171)
  - Other Accounts, 1934-1944; 6
    - Absorbine Jr. (Young)--Meet Your Voice, 1940 Nov. 28 (Film-reel 171)
    - American magazine--American Scene, 1935 July 8 (Film-reel 170)
    - American Tobacco (Half & Half), 1935 (Film-reel 170)
    - Bromo-Seltzer (Emerson Drug), 1935 June 3 (Film-reel 170)
    - Buxton--Schenectady production, 1944 Apr. 19 (Film-reel 215)
    - Cutex (Northam Warren), 1935 (Film-reel 170)
    - Elgin, 1935 (Film-reel 170)
    - Elgin--Dale Carnegie, 1941 (Film-reel 170)
    - John Kuhne's script, 1944 Sept. 18 (Film-reel 215)
    - Johns-Manville--You Can Be Successful, 1935 (Film-reel 170)
    - Libby McNeil & Libby, 1941 May 18 (Film-reel 170)
    - Marionette Show--Charlie McCarthy, Worlds Fair, 1940 (Film-reel 171)
      Scope and Contents
      By Sue Hastings
    - N.Y. State Assn. of Architects--So You're Going to Build, 1941 Apr. 17 (Film-reel 170)
    - Old Gold cigarettes (Lorillard)--Strictly G.I., 1940 Dec. 19 (Film-reel 171)
    - Philco--John Doe American, 1941 Dec. 15 (Film-reel 170)
    - Planter's Cocktail Peanuts, 1939 Dec. (Film-reel 170)
    - Planter's Peanuts--Name It and Claim It, 1940 Nov. 26 (Film-reel 171)
    - Planters--The Peanut is a Serious Guy, 1944 May 24 (Film-reel 215)
    - Royal Gelatine (Standard Brands)--Jeeves, 1934 July 24 (Film-reel 170)
    - Royal Gelatine (Standard Brands)--Wodehouse memo, 1939 Aug. 2 (Film-reel 170)
    - Script (no client)--Race of Hearts, 1940 (Film-reel 171)
    - Script (no client)--Soldier from the Wars Returning, 1940 (Film-reel 171)
    - Script (no commercials or clients named), 1940 Dec. (Film-reel 171)
    - Shell, 1935; 1937 (Film-reel 170)
    - Shell Television, 1940 Dec. (Film-reel 171)
    - Ward's Tip Top Bread--Phil Cook Show, 1941 Nov. 18 (Film-reel 170)
    - Ward's Tip Top Bread--The Secret Three, 1941 Dec. 30 (Film-reel 170)
    - White Owl cigars (General Cigar), 1935 (Film-reel 170)
    - White Owl cigars--Who-Who, 1939 May 29 (Film-reel 171)
    - Writers' War Board--Good Company, 1943 (Film-reel 201)
    - You And Your Dog (Defense Dog), 1943 (Film-reel 201)
- B.F. Goodrich, 1930-1931; 5
  - Defiance Tire radio program, 1930; 7
    - Don Quixote, 1930 (Film-reel 8)
    - Gareth and Lynette, 1930 (Film-reel 8)
    - Geraint and Enid, 1930 (Film-reel 8)
    - Guinevere, 1930 (Film-reel 8)
    - Horatius at the Bridge, 1930 (Film-reel 8)
    - Horatius at the Bridge, 1930 (Film-reel 8)
    - Joan of Arc, 1930 (Film-reel 8)
    - Richard the Lionhearted, 1930 (Film-reel 8)
    - Sir Lancelot, 1930 (Film-reel 8)
    - Tristan and Isolde, 1930 (Film-reel 8)
    - William Tell, 1930 (Film-reel 8)
  - Other Programming, 1930-1931; 8
    - Silver Fleet, approximately 1930 (Film-reel 8)
    - Uncle Abe and David, 1930-1931 (Film-reel 8)
    - Uncle Abe and David, 1930-1931 (Film-reel 9)
- Believe It Or Not (Sponsor unidentified), 1950; 6
  - Corpus Delecti (Director's copy), 1950 Aug. 17 (Film-reel 1003)
  - Cross of Valor (Director's copy), 1950 Mar. 15 (Film-reel 1003)
  - Death Calls the Tune (Director's copy), 1950 June 8 (Film-reel 1003)
  - Double Jeopardy (Director's copy), 1950 July 13 (Film-reel 1003)
  - Journey Through Darkness (Director's copy), 1950 Mar. 1 (Film-reel 1003)
  - Loser Take All (Director's copy), 1950 Aug. 3 (Film-reel 1003)
  - Murder to Come (Director's copy), 1950 Mar. 8 (Film-reel 1003)
  - Murder With a Payoff, 1950 July 27 (Film-reel 1003)
  - Passage to Zermatt (Director's copy), 1950 June 1 (Film-reel 1003)
  - The Blood Call, 1950 Aug. 31 (Film-reel 1003)
  - The Bodark Tree (Director's copy), 1950 May 18 (Film-reel 1003)
  - The Case of the Missing Model (Director's copy), 1950 Feb. 15 (Film-reel 1003)
  - The Diamond Eye (Director's copy), 1950 Feb. 22 (Film-reel 1003)
  - The Emerald Tattoo (Director's copy), 1950 Aug. 24 (Film-reel 1003)
  - The Ghostly Will (Director's copy), 1950 Aug. 10 (Film-reel 1003)
  - The Million Dollar Corpse (Director's copy), 1950 July 6 (Film-reel 1003)
  - The Mystery of the Missing Guest, 1950 May 10 (Film-reel 1003)
  - The Silent Witness (Director's copy), 1950 May 25 (Film-reel 1003)
  - Wheels of Chance, 1950 Feb. 1 (Film-reel 1003)
- Block Drug Co., 1942-1944; 7
  - Dentu-Grip, 1942-1944; 9
    - Commercials, 1942 June-July (Film-reel 171)
    - Commercials, 1942 Sept.-Nov. (Film-reel 205)
    - Commercials, 1943 June-Nov. (Film-reel 205)
    - Commercials, 1944 Jan.-Apr. (Film-reel 205)
  - Gold Medal capsules, 1942-1944; 10
    - Commercials, 1942 July-Dec. (Film-reel 171)
    - Commercials, 1942 May-Aug. (Film-reel 205)
    - Commercials, 1943 Jan.-Sept. (Film-reel 205)
    - Commercials, 1944 Mar.-July (Film-reel 205)
    - Dentu-Grip, commercials, 1942 May (Film-reel 205)
    - Dentu-Grip, commercials, 1943 Mar. 25 (Film-reel 205)
    - Spot announcements, 1944 Apr. 16 (Film-reel 235)
- Brillo Manufacturing Company, 1946-1956; 8
  - Programming, 1946-1955; 11
    - Commercials, 1947 Jan.-Apr.; 1947 Oct.-1948 Jan. (Film-reel 360)
    - Polly the Shopper commercials, 1948 Jan.-Feb. (Film-reel 418)
    - Racket Squad, 1955 (Film-reel 1001)
    - Racket Squad television, 1954 (Film-reel 990)
    - Sammy Kaye Show, 1954 Aug.-Dec. (Film-reel 990)
    - Sammy Kaye Show, 1955 Jan. (Film-reel 1001)
    - Your Neighbor Lady commercials, 1946 Oct.-Dec. (Film-reel 306)
  - TV Star Tonight, 1955-1956; 12
    - A Door You Can Close, 1956 Apr. 12 (Film-reel 1004)
    - A Matter of Life, 1955 Mar. 24 (Film-reel 1002)
    - A Night Visitor, 1956 Jan. 19 (Film-reel 1004)
    - A Small Glass Bottle, 1956 June 7 (Film-reel 1004)
    - A Trip To Czardis, 1956 May 17 (Film-reel 1004)
    - An Ambulance for Jill, 1956 Apr. 19 (Film-reel 1004)
    - Below Average, 1956 Feb. 2 (Film-reel 1004)
    - Blood Call, 1956 July 19 (Film-reel 1004)
    - Boy Crazy, 1956 Mar. 29 (Film-reel 1004)
    - Can You Coffee Pot On Skates, 1956 May 3 (Film-reel 1004)
    - Concerning Death, 1955 Feb. 17 (Film-reel 1002)
    - Concerning Death, 1955 Feb. 17 (Film-reel 1011)
      Repeat of broadcast microfilmed on reel 1002
    - Cross-Words, 1955 June 23 (Film-reel 1002)
    - Death of a Stranger, 1955 Mar. 31 (Film-reel 1002)
    - Death of a Stranger, 1955 Mar. 31 (Film-reel 1011)
    - Early Frost, 1956 Jan. 26 (Film-reel 1004)
    - Edge of Light, 1955 Aug. 4 (Film-reel 1002)
    - Finders Keepers, 1955 Oct. 27 (Film-reel 1002)
    - Flame and Ice, 1955 Aug. 25 (Film-reel 1002)
    - Footfalls, 1955 July 7 (Film-reel 1002)
    - Gang-Up, 1955 Dec. 15 (Film-reel 1002)
    - Golden Victory, 1955 May 26 (Film-reel 1002)
    - Golden Victory, 1955 May 26 (Film-reel 1011)
    - Have Faith and Have Patience, 1956 May 24 (Film-reel 1004)
    - Have Faith in Your Agent, 1955 Nov. 24 (Film-reel 1002)
    - How Beautiful with Shoes, 1955 Feb. 24 (Film-reel 1002)
    - How Beautiful with Shoes, 1955 Feb. 24 (Film-reel 1011)
    - Ile, 1955 Mar. 10 (Film-reel 1002)
    - Ile (Eugene O'Neill), 1955 Mar. 10 (Film-reel 1011)
    - Kingdom's Child, 1956 May 31 (Film-reel 1004)
    - Long Distance, 1955 Sept. 15 (Film-reel 1002)
    - Love Is A Lawyer, 1956 Mar. 15 (Film-reel 1004)
    - Matter of Life, 1955 Mar. 24 (Film-reel 1011)
    - Mr. Bell's Creation, 1956 June 28 (Film-reel 1004)
    - Night Be Quiet, 1955 Nov. 3 (Film-reel 1002)
    - Night Escape, 1956 Mar. 8 (Film-reel 1004)
    - Nightmare By Day, 1955 Dec. 8 (Film-reel 1002)
    - Not for Me, 1955 Oct. 6 (Film-reel 1002)
    - One Day More, 1955 Oct. 13 (Film-reel 1002)
    - Racket Squad, 1956 Jan.-Aug. (Film-reel 1004)
    - Rite of Love, 1956 Feb. 23 (Film-reel 1004)
    - Second String, 1955 May 12 (Film-reel 1011)
    - Shadow of Evil, 1956 July 5 (Film-reel 1004)
    - Strength of Steel, 1955 June 16 (Film-reel 1002)
    - Success Story, 1955 Sept. 8 (Film-reel 1002)
    - Taste, 1955 June 2 (Film-reel 1002)
    - Taste, 1955 June 2 (Film-reel 1011)
    - Tender Roots, 1955 May 19 (Film-reel 1002)
    - Tender Roots, 1955 May 19 (Film-reel 1011)
    - The Ascent of P.J. O'Hara, 1956 June 21 (Film-reel 1004)
    - The Big Fifteenth, 1956 Jan. 5 (Film-reel 1004)
    - The Cage, 1955 Nov. 17 (Film-reel 1002)
    - The Chevigny Man, 1956 Mar. 22 (Film-reel 1004)
    - The Coffee Shop Incident, 1956 July 12 (Film-reel 1004)
    - The College Hour, 1955 May 12 (Film-reel 1002)
    - The Critic, 1955 July 14 (Film-reel 1002)
    - The Dark Search, 1955 May 5 (Film-reel 1002)
    - The Dark Search, 1955 May 5 (Film-reel 1011)
    - The Gallant Lady, 1955 June 30 (Film-reel 1002)
    - The Gentleman Caller, 1956 Aug. 2 (Film-reel 1004)
    - The Giants Stair, 1955 Apr. 21 (Film-reel 1002)
    - The Giants' Stair, 1955 Apr. 21 (Film-reel 1011)
    - The Girl, 1956 May 10 (Film-reel 1004)
    - The Happy Journey, 1956 Feb. 9 (Film-reel 1004)
    - The Kewpie Doll, 1955 July 21 (Film-reel 1002)
    - The Lavender Kite, 1955 Apr. 14 (Film-reel 1002)
    - The Lavender Kite, 1955 Apr. 14 (Film-reel 1011)
    - The Little Wife, 1955 Oct. 20 (Film-reel 1002)
    - The Long View, 1956 June 14 (Film-reel 1004)
    - The Matrimony Shop, 1955 July 28 (Film-reel 1002)
    - The Mirthmakers, 1956 Aug. 9 (Film-reel 1004)
    - The Murderer, 1955 Mar. 17 (Film-reel 1002)
    - The Murderer, 1955 Mar. 17 (Film-reel 1011)
    - The Prom, 1955 Aug. 18 (Film-reel 1002)
    - The Ring of General Macias, 1955 Aug. 11 (Film-reel 1002)
    - The Ryan Girl, 1955 Nov. 10 (Film-reel 1002)
    - The Selfish Giant, 1955 Dec. 22 (Film-reel 1002)
    - The Summer Road, 1955 Dec. 1 (Film-reel 1002)
    - The Terrible Woman, 1955 Sept. 29 (Film-reel 1002)
    - The Thing That Never Happened, 1956 Feb. 16 (Film-reel 1004)
    - Three Hours Between Planes, 1956 Mar. 1 (Film-reel 1004)
    - Tough Boy, 1956 Apr. 26 (Film-reel 1004)
    - Treasure Trove, 1955 Apr. 7 (Film-reel 1002)
    - Treasure Trove, 1955 Apr. 7 (Film-reel 1011)
    - Trifles, 1955 Sept. 1 (Film-reel 1002)
    - Two Windows, 1956 Apr. 5 (Film-reel 1004)
    - Visitation, 1955 Sept. 22 (Film-reel 1002)
    - Wanted: Poor Boy, 1955 June 9 (Film-reel 1002)
    - Weekend, 1955 Feb. 10 (Film-reel 1002)
    - Weekend, 1955 Feb. 10 (Film-reel 1011)
    - Will Power, 1956 July 26 (Film-reel 1004)
    - With Glory and Honor, 1956 Jan. 12 (Film-reel 1004)
    - Write Me a Love Scene, 1955 Dec. 29 (Film-reel 1002)
    - You Need Me, 1955 Feb. 3 (Film-reel 1002)
    - You Need Me, 1955 Feb. 3 (Film-reel 1011)
    - Zero Hour, 1955 Apr. 28 (Film-reel 1002)
    - Zero Hour, 1955 Apr. 28 (Film-reel 1011)
    - Zone of Quiet, 1955 Mar. 3 (Film-reel 1002)
    - Zone of Quiet, 1955 Mar. 3 (Film-reel 1011)
- Calsodent, 1929-1940; 9
  - Bob Howard, 1939 (Film-reel 133)
  - Bob Howard, 1940 Jan.-Apr. (Film-reel 174)
  - KPRC Houston Tex., 1929 July-Aug. (Film-reel 132)
  - Lewis Dean, 1930 Dec. (Film-reel 132)
  - Marley R. Sherris, 1930 Mar.-Dec. (Film-reel 132)
  - Marley R. Sherris, 1931-1932 Apr. (Film-reel 132)
  - Marley R. Sherris, 1932 May-1934 July (Film-reel 133)
  - Robert T. Colwell, 1930 Sept.-Nov. (Film-reel 132)
  - WAAT, 1930 Apr.-June (Film-reel 132)
  - WEAF, 1929 May-Aug. (Film-reel 132)
- Carter's Products (Superin), 1943-1944; 10
  - Commercials, 1944 Jan.-Feb. (Film-reel 215)
  - Keepsakes, 1943 Sept. 19 (Film-reel 201)
  - Keepsakes, 1943 Sept. 19 (Film-reel 202)
  - Spot announcements, 1943 June-Dec. (Film-reel 201)
- CIBA--Medical Horizone, 1955-1957; 11
  - 2. Beyond the Mask, 1956 Sept. 16 (Film-reel 1005)
  - 4. One Out of Ten, 1956 Sept. 30 (Film-reel 1005)
  - 6. Man Under Sea, 1956 Oct. 14 (Film-reel 1005)
  - 8. Most Happy Time, 1956 Oct. 28 (Film-reel 1005)
  - 10. Kine, 1956 Nov. 11 (Film-reel 1006)
  - 12. Happy Children, 1956 Nov. 25 (Film-reel 1005)
  - 12. Happy Children, 1956 Nov. 25 (Film-reel 1006)
  - 14. Bone Engineering, 1956 Dec. 9 (Film-reel 1006)
  - 16. Christmas in Community Hospital, 1956 Dec. 23 (Film-reel 1006)
  - 18. The Hidden Disease, 1957 Jan. 6 (Film-reel 1006)
  - 20. When Emergency Strikes, 1957 Jan. 20 (Film-reel 1006)
  - 22. Report on Cancer, 1957 Feb. 3 (Film-reel 1006)
  - 23. High Blood Pressure, 1957 Feb. 10 (Film-reel 1006)
  - 25. Operation CVA, 1957 Feb. 24 (Film-reel 1006)
  - 27. Radiology, 1957 Mar. 10 (Film-reel 1006)
  - 29. Psychosomatic Med, 1957 Mar. 24 (Film-reel 1006)
  - 31. Deafness, 1957 Apr. 7 (Film-reel 1006)
  - 33. A Triumph and a Challenge, 1957 Apr. 21 (Film-reel 1006)
  - 35. Legal Medicine, 1957 May 5 (Film-reel 1006)
  - 37. Burns, 1957 May 19 (Film-reel 1006)
  - 39. Radiology, 1957 June 2 (Film-reel 1006)
  - Television, 1955 Sept.-Dec. (Film-reel 1001)
  - Television, 1956 Jan.-Mar.; Oct. (Film-reel 1003)
- City Baking Co. (Rice Bakeries), 1930-1941; 12
  - Baltimore and Washington, 1930-1939 (Film-reel 139)
    incomplete series
  - Commercials, 1941 Apr. (Film-reel 170)
  - Commercials, 1939 Sept.-1940 Sept. (Film-reel 173)
  - Commercials--Washington and Baltimore, 1940 Jan.-Oct. (Film-reel 173)
    Incomplete series
  - Rice's School Lunch Loaf, 1940 Feb.; Sept. (Film-reel 173)
- Cream of Wheat, 1929-1936; 13
  - Jolly Bill and Jane, 1929-1933; 13
    - 1929 Jan.-1932 May (Film-reel 4)
    - 1932 May-Dec. (Film-reel 5)
    - 1932 Dec. -1933 Apr. (Film-reel 6)
    - 1933 Mar. 13 (Film-reel 120)
      See reel 6 for rest of script
  - Other Programming, 1929-1936; 14
    - Alexander Woollcott Town Crier, 1934 Oct.-1935 Dec. (Film-reel 7)
    - Alexander Woollcott, Town Crier, 1935 Oct. 6 (Film-reel 342)
      California Office
    - Angelo Patri, 1931 Aug.-1933 Dec. (Film-reel 6)
    - Angelo Patri, 1933 Dec.-1934 Apr. (Film-reel 7)
    - Buck Rogers, 1936 (Film-reel 7)
    - Buck Rogers, 1936 (Film-reel 8)
    - Rastus, Cream of Wheat Menagerie, 1929 (Film-reel 4)
    - Sigmund Romberg, 1935 Sept.-Dec. (Film-reel 120)
- Eastman Kodak, 1930-1954; 14
  - Kodak Family Adventure, approximately 1954; 15
    - America Discovers the Osbornes, approximately 1954 (Film-reel 1007)
    - An Act of Congress, approximately 1954 (Film-reel 1007)
    - An Act of Congress, screenplay, approximately 1954 (Film-reel 1007)
    - Barbara and the Touring Players, approximately 1954 (Film-reel 1007)
    - Baseball Hall of Fame, approximately 1954 (Film-reel 1007)
    - Basic Story Outline, approximately 1954 (Film-reel 1007)
    - Betty Discovers Wisconsin, approximately 1954 (Film-reel 1007)
    - Character Descriptions: Barbara, approximately 1954 (Film-reel 1007)
    - Character Descriptions: Betty, approximately 1954 (Film-reel 1007)
    - Character Descriptions: Jim, approximately 1954 (Film-reel 1007)
    - Character Descriptions: Teddy, approximately 1954 (Film-reel 1007)
    - College Episode, approximately 1954 (Film-reel 1007)
    - Diplomatic Incident, approximately 1954 (Film-reel 1007)
    - Florida Fish Story, approximately 1954 (Film-reel 1007)
    - Foreword--Role of Picture Taking, approximately 1954 (Film-reel 1007)
    - Four Rooms with a View, approximately 1954 (Film-reel 1007)
    - Hermit of Berthoud Pass, approximately 1954 (Film-reel 1007)
    - Indiana University Story, approximately 1954 (Film-reel 1007)
    - Indiana University Story, screenplay, approximately 1954 (Film-reel 1007)
    - Initiation, approximately 1954 (Film-reel 1007)
    - Little Red Schoolhouse, approximately 1954 (Film-reel 1007)
    - Little Red Schoolhouse, screenplay, approximately 1954 (Film-reel 1007)
    - Martha's Vineyard Story, approximately 1954 (Film-reel 1007)
    - Osbornes Find a House, approximately 1954 (Film-reel 1007)
    - Pay-Dirt, approximately 1954 (Film-reel 1007)
    - Riverdale Revisited, approximately 1954 (Film-reel 1007)
    - Road Black, approximately 1954 (Film-reel 1007)
    - Roots--Boston, approximately 1954 (Film-reel 1007)
    - Shopping Trip, approximately 1954 (Film-reel 1007)
    - Table of Contents, approximately 1954 (Film-reel 1007)
    - Teddy and the Magician, approximately 1954 (Film-reel 1007)
    - Teddy and the Magician, screenplay, approximately 1954 (Film-reel 1007)
    - Teddy and the Modern Painting, approximately 1954 (Film-reel 1007)
    - Teddy and the Shanty-Boaters, approximately 1954 (Film-reel 1007)
    - The 86th Floor, approximately 1954 (Film-reel 1007)
    - The Ben Franklin Desk, approximately 1954 (Film-reel 1007)
    - The Brooklyn Story, approximately 1954 (Film-reel 1007)
    - The Capistrano Pigeon, approximately 1954 (Film-reel 1007)
    - The Charleston Story, approximately 1954 (Film-reel 1007)
    - The Chicago Story, approximately 1954 (Film-reel 1007)
    - The Christman Story, approximately 1954 (Film-reel 1007)
    - The Gettysburg Story, approximately 1954 (Film-reel 1007)
    - The Iowa Story, approximately 1954 (Film-reel 1007)
    - The Klamath Falls Story, approximately 1954 (Film-reel 1007)
    - The Little Green Bag, approximately 1954 (Film-reel 1007)
    - The Natchez Recluse, approximately 1954 (Film-reel 1007)
    - The New House, approximately 1954 (Film-reel 1007)
    - The Newport Story, approximately 1954 (Film-reel 1007)
    - The North Carolina Story, approximately 1954 (Film-reel 1007)
    - The Old Flames, approximately 1954 (Film-reel 1007)
    - The Old House, approximately 1954 (Film-reel 1007)